<data>
  <jewelry>
    <name>Ear Lobe Cuff Earrings</name>
    <price>17,000</price>
    <desc>
      Handcrafted in 14-karat solid gold, the Ear Lobe Cuff Earrings are sleek, edgy, and
      straightforward in design.
    </desc>
  </jewelry>
  <jewelry>
    <name>Hear Locket Necklace</name>
    <price>32,000</price>
    <desc>
      Beautifully handcrafted in 14-karat solid gold, this charming heart-shaped locket is
      a sweet addition to your chains.
    </desc>
  </jewelry>
  <jewelry>
    <name>Bubble Barely There Bracelet</name>
    <price>4,0000</price>
    <desc>
      Barely There Bracelet – This 14-karat yellow gold Barely There link bracelet is a
      classic minimal chain for the perfect understated look.
    </desc>
  </jewelry>
  <jewelry>
    <name>Bold Round Diamond Link Ring</name>
    <price>21,000</price>
    <desc>
      14-karat gold Bold Round Diamond Link Ring with striking chunky chain design
      encrusted with pavé round cut natural diamonds.
    </desc>
  </jewelry>
  <jewelry>
    <name>Classic Cross Pendant</name>
    <price>23,000</price>
    <desc>
      This classic staple is the perfect piece to add detail to your outfit. 
      The sharp design lends an eye-catching interest to a sentimental pendant.
    </desc>
  </jewelry>
  <jewelry>
    <name>Cushion Signet Ring with Black Onyx</name>
    <price>45,000</price>
    <desc>
      Embody a modern masculinity with this bold cushion signet ring. 
      The focal point of the ring is the handsomely polished onyx stone which sits at the center of its high-polished finish band.
    </desc>
  </jewelry>
  <jewelry>
    <name>Dua Asymmetric Anklet</name>
    <price>5,000</price>
    <desc>
      An upgrade to your sneaker and sandal game — add a little sparkle to your ankle 
      with this stunning 14-karat yellow gold asymmetric anklet with half round and half elongated links.
    </desc>
  </jewelry>
  <jewelry>
    <name>Bar Bracelet</name>
    <price>5,000</price>
    <desc>
      Contemporary and timeless, this smooth and polished bar on a dainty bracelet 
      chain is crafted with 14-karat solid gold and offers a lifetime of daily wear.
    </desc>
  </jewelry>
   <jewelry>
    <name>Ultra Fine Technicolor Ring</name>
    <price>15,000</price>
    <desc>
      Playful yet refined, the Ultra Fine Technicolor Ring is crafted in 14-karat solid gold set with an 
      assortment of colored semi-precious stones that add a delicate dose of rainbow sparkle.
    </desc>
  </jewelry>
  <jewelry>
    <name>Claw Pearl Studs</name>
    <price>10,000</price>
    <desc>
      Perfect for everyday wear, you can never go wrong with these 100% natural 
      freshwater timeless beauties in three prong 14-karat solid gold setting.
    </desc>
  </jewelry>
</data>
